Picture Collection LSC.0099.a
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Tahoe, Lake -- Views (Mt. Tallac)., 7 items (Folder 41)
- Tahoe, Lake -- Views., 37 items (Folder 33)
- Talley, Marion, 1907-1983, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 78, Folder 42)
- Taos, N.M., 138 items (Box 78, Folder 43)
- Tatoosh Mountains, Wash. -- Views., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Tauchnitz, Bernard, freiherr von, 1816-1895, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Taylor, Bayard., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Taylor, Maria (Ternan) "Mrs. Rowland Taylor", b.1836-1838? -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Taylor, Zachary, pres. U.S., 1784-1850, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Taylorsville, Plumas County, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Tecate, Mex. -- Views., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Tedford, Adeline Matalia (Alvarado)., 2 items (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Tefft, Henry H., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Tehama County, Calif., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Telegraphy -- Views., 31 items (Folder 11)
- Telephone -- Apparatus and Supplies -- Views., 11 items (Folder 12)
- Telephone -- Automatic -- Views., 3 items (Folder 13)
- Telephone -- History -- Views., 46 items (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Telephone -- Lines -- Views., 14 items (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Telephone -- Power-Plants -- Views., 3 items (Folder 16)
- Telephone -- Switchboards -- Views., 16 items (Folder 17)
- Teletype -- Views., 10 items (Folder 18)
- Television -- Views., 16 items (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Tellegen, Lou, 1881-1934, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Telluride, Colo. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 21)
- Temecula Canyon, Calif., 1 item (Folder 23)
- Temecula, Calif., 3 items (Folder 22)
- Temescal Valley., 4 items (Box 79, Folder 24)
- Temple, John, 1798-1866., 3 items (Box 79, Folder 25)
- Temple, Sam., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Temples, India -- Views., 3 items (Folder 27)
- Tennessee (State) -- Views., 2 items (Folder 28)
- Tennyson, Alfred., 2 items (Box 79, Folder 29)
- Teresa, Saint, 1515-1582, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 32)
- Ternan, Frances Eleanor (Jarman), 1803?-1873., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Terry, Kate, 1844-1924, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Texas -- Views., 2 items (Folder 33)
- Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1811-1863, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 79, Folder 34)
- Tholler -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 35)
- Thomas, C.C. -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 36)
- Thomas, Dylan, 1914-1953., 1 item (Folder 37)
- Thomas, John Charles, 1891-1960, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 38)
- Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1884-1968, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 39)
- Thomas, Theodore, 1835-1905., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 40)
- Thompson, Alpheus B., 1797-1869, -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 41)
- Thompson, Dorothy, 1894-1961, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 42)
- Thompson, Frank., 2 items (Folder 43)
- Thompson, George., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 44)
- Thompson, Hunter S., 1 item (Box 79, Folder 45)
- Tibbetts, George P., 1 item (Folder 46)
- Timbucktoo, Calif., 1 item (Folder 47)
- Timms, A.W. -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 48)
- Tires, Rubber -- Views., 4 items (Box 79, Folder 49)
- Toklas, Alice Babette -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 79, Folder 50)
- Tombstone, Arizona., 5 items (Folder 52)
- Tonopah, Nev. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 1)
- Toole, John Lawrence, 1830-1906, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 2)
- Topanga Canyon, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 10 items (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Topeka, Kansas -- Views., 1 item (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Tostoi, Ilia Lvovich, graf, 1866-1934., 1 item (Folder 51)
- Townsend, Francis Everett, 1867-1960, -- Portrait., 6 items (Folder 5)
- Toys -- Views., 14 items (Folder 6)
- Trabuco Canyon, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Transportation -- Calif. -- Views., 29 items (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Transportation -- Views. (see also Automobiles, Railroads -- Views, etc.), 38 items (Folder 9)
- Transportation. (Folder 8)
- Treager, W.I., 1 item (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Tresidder, Donald Bertrand, 1894-1948., 1 item (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Trinidad, Colo. -- Views., 38 items (Folder 12)
- Trinity County, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 13)
- Trollope Family., 2 items (Folder 14)
- Trollope, Anthony, 1815-1882, -- Portrait., 4 items (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Trollope, Mrs. Frances Eleanor (Ternan), 1835-1913., 2 items (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Trona, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 17)
- Trotier-Beaubien, Charles H., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Troutdale, Colo. -- Views., 20 items (Folder 19)
- Truckee River Dam, Nevada -- Views., 1 item (Box 80, Folder 21)
- Truckee, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 80, Folder 20)
- Truth, Sojourner, d.1883, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Tuba City, Arizona -- Views., 11 items (Folder 23)
- Tubac Presisio, Arizona Territory., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Tucker, Sophie, 1884-1966. (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Tucker, Sophie, 1884-1966., 11 items (Box 80, Folder 25)
- Tucker, Sophie, 1884-1966. (folder 1 or 2) (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Tulare, Calif. -- Views., 10 items (Box 80, Folder 26)
- Tully, Jim, 1888-1947., 1 item (Box 80, Folder 27)
- Tuolumne, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Box 80, Folder 28)
- Tupper, Martin Farquhar, 1810-1889., 2 items (Box 80, Folder 29)
- Turkey -- Views., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Turlock, Calif. -- Views., 8 items (Folder 31)
- Turner, Maud - Residence. (Folder 11)
- Tuscon, Arizona -- Views., 3 items (Box 80, Folder 32)
- Tuttletown., 3 items (Box 80, Folder 33)
- Twentynine Palms, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 34)
- Typewriters -- Views., 7 items (Folder 1)
- Tyrone, N.M. -- Views., 22 items (Folder 2)
- U.S. - Emigration and Immigration -- Views., 6 items (Box 15, Folder 39)
- U.S. Army -- Uniforms., 5 items (Box 81, Folder 4)
- U.S. Army. 13th New York Regiment -- Portrait., 36 items (Folder 3)
- U.S. History -- Civil War -- Views., 51 items (Folder 5)
- U.S. History - Revolution -- Views. (Folder 1)
- U.S. History -- War of 1898 -- Views., 3 items (Box 81, Folder 6)
- U.S. Naval Academy, Annapolis -- Cadets -- Portraits., 66 items (Box 81, Folder 7)
- U.S. Works Projects Administration Photographs., 23 items (Folder 8)
- Universal City, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Universities & Colleges -- California (see also: names of individual institutions)., 8 items (Folder 10)
- University of Southern California., 87 items (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Unruh, Jesse, 1922-1987, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Urquart, Isabelle., 1 item (Folder 13)
- Utah -- University., 26 items (Folder 14)
- Utah -- Views., 18 items (Folder 15)
- Valentine, L.H., 1 item (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Valery, Paul, 1871-1945., 1 item (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Valle, del, Family -- Portrait., 8 items (Folder 18)
- Vall?e, Rudy, 1901-1986., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Vallejo Family -- Portrait., 8 items (Folder 20)
- Valley of the Moon, San Bernardino County, Calif., 1 item (Box 81, Folder 21)
- Valley Ranch, N.M. -- Views., 7 items (Box 81, Folder 22)
- Valparaiso (City)., 25 items (Folder 1)
- Van Dyke, William M., 2 items (Folder 3)
- Van Horn, Louise Taylor (Gerdine)., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Van Nuys, Annis., 1 item (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Van Nuys., 48 items (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 7)
- Vandegrift, Alexander Archer, 1887-1973., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Vanderbilt Family -- Portrait. (Folder 13)
- Vasquez Rocks, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Vasquez, Tiburcio., 9 items (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Veczey, Franz Von -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Vejar Family -- Portrait., 8 items (Folder 11)
- Venice -- Views. (Folder 12)
- Venice, Calif., 17 items (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Ventura., 46 items (Folder 13)
- Verdugo., 2 items (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Vernal, Utah -- Views., 1 item (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Vernet, Emile Jean Horace, 1 item (Box 82, Folder 16)
- Verross, Carl -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Victoria, Queen of Great Britain, 1819-1901., 2 items (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Victorville, Calif., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Vienna., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Vieuxtemps, H. -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Vieuxtemps, Henri F.J., 1820-1881, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 82, Folder 22)
- Villa Family -- Portraits., 2 items (Box 82, Folder 23)
- Vinson, Frederick Moore, 1890-1953, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Virginia City, Nevada., 17 items (Folder 25)
- Visalia, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 26)
- Viscaino, Sebastian, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 82, Folder 27)
- Vischer, Edward, 1809-1879., 1 item (Box 82, Folder 28)
- Volcano., 3 items (Folder 29)
- Voyages and Travels., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Vroman, Adam Clark, 1856-1916., 1 item (Folder 31)
- W.D. Miller Club of First AME Church of Los Angeles., 1 item (Box 83, Folder 30)
- Waesche, Russell Randolph, 1886-1946, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Wagner, Henry Raup, 1862-1957., 8 items (Folder 2)
- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883, -- Performances -- Bayreuth., 11 items (Folder 3)
- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Wagner, Robert Ferdinand, 1877-1953., 1 item (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Wagon Mound, N.M. -- Views., 7 items (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Wagon Wheel Gap, Colo. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 7)
- Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew, 1883-1953, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew, 1883-1953, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 8)
- Walker, G.H., 1 item (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Walker, George C., 1 item (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Wallace, Alfred Russell, 1823-1913., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Wallace, George M., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Walpi, Arizona -- Views., 2 items (Folder 13)
- Walter, Bruno, 1876-1962, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Ward, Colo. -- Views., 4 items (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Ward, Mary Augusta (Arnold) "Mrs. Humphry Ward," 1851-1920., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Warner, Solomon., 1 item (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Warner's Hot Springs., 9 items (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Warner's Ranch., 20 items (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Warren, Earl, 1891-1974, -- Portrait., 53 items (Box 83, Folder 20)
- Warren, Earl, 1891-1974., 1 item (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Warren, James Lloyd LaFayette, 1805-1896., 1 item (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Warren, Samuel, 1807-1877., 3 items (Box 83, Folder 22)
- Warren, William C., 1837-1870., 4 items (Box 83, Folder 23)
- Warships -- Views., 15 items (Box 83, Folder 24)
- Washington (State) -- Views., 5 items (Folder 26)
- Washington (State) -- Views. (folder 1 of 2), 5 items (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Washington (State) -- Views. (folder 2 of 2), 7 items (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Washington State. (folder 1 of 2) (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Washington, D.C., 37 items (Box 83, Folder 25)
- Water-Supply -- California, Southern., 30 items (Folder 27)
- Watkins Glen, New York -- Views., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Watsonville, Calif. -- Views., 31 items (Folder 29)
- Weaverville., 20 items (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Webb, Harry., 3 items (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Webster, Ben, 1864-1947., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Wedekind, Erika -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Weinstock, Matt, 1903-1970., 2 items (Folder 5)
- Weir, Harrison William, 1824-1906., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Weissmuller, Johnny., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Welch, D'Alt? Aldridge, 1907-1970, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Welch, Denton, 1915-1948, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 9)
- Wellborn, Olin., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Weller, Dana., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Weller, Sam -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Wellington, Athur Wellesley, 1st duke of, 1769-1852., 1 item (Folder 13)
- Wellman, Paul Iselin, 1898-, 2 items (Folder 14)
- Wells, Herbert George, 1866-1946, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Wells, Nev. -- Views., 7 items (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Wentworth, Helen., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Werfel, Franz V., 1890-1945, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Wescott, Glenway, 1901-1987, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 19)
- West Indies -- Views., 92 items (Folder 22)
- Westbury, Richard Bethell, 1st baron, 1800-1873., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Westergaard, Waldemar Christian, 1882-1963., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Westwood Villiage (West Lost Angeles)., 5 items (Folder 24)
- Westwood, Calif. -- Views., 11 items (Box 84, Folder 23)
- Wheeler, Benjamin Ide, 1854-1927., 2 items (Box 84, Folder 25)
- Wheeler, John Ozeas., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 26)
- Wheeler, Springs, Calif. -- Views., 21 items (Box 84, Folder 27)
- Whitaker, Robert, 1863-1944., 1 item (Folder 28)
- White Sands, New Mexico., 1 item (Folder 31)
- White, Michael Claringbuld, 1802-1885?, 8 items (Folder 29)
- White, Stephen Mallory, 1853-1901., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 30)
- Whiteman, Paul, 1890-1964, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 84, Folder 32)
- Whiteside, Arthur Dare., 1 item (Folder 33)
- Whiting Family., 3 items (Folder 34)
- Whitley Park Canyon Club., 51 items (Folder 36)
- Whitley, Hobart Johnstone., 6 items (Box 84, Folder 35)
- Whitman, Walt, 1819-1892., 5 items (Box 84, Folder 37)
- Whitney, Mount, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Whitsett, W. Paul, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 38)
- Whitter College, Whittier, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Folder 40)
- Whittier State School., 1 item (Box 84, Folder 41)
- Whittier, Calif. -- Views., 38 items (Box 84, Folder 39)
- Wickard, Claude Raymond, 1893-1967., 1 item (Folder 42)
- Widney, Robert M., 3 items (Folder 43)
- Wieniawski, Henri, 1835-1880, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 44)
- Wiggin, Kate Douglas (Smith), 1856-1923., 3 items (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Wiggin, Kate Douglas. (Folder 14)
- Wiggins, Frank., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Wilbur Springs, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Wilde, Oscar, 1854-1900, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Wilder, Laura Ingalls, 1867-1967, -- Portrait., 9 items (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Wilhelmj, August, 1845-1908., 3 items (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Willard, N.M. -- Views., 9 items (Folder 7)
- Willat Studios -- Views., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Williams, Ben Ames, 1889-1953, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Williams, Benjamin T., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Williams, C.N., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Williams, Frayne -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 12)
- Willkie, Wendell Lewis, 1892-1944, -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 13)
- Wilson, Benjamin Davis, 1811-1878., 7 items (Folder 14)
- Wilson, Mt., 2 items (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Wilson, Peter., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Wilson, Richard, 1714-1782., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Wilson, Thomas B., 1 item (Folder 17)
- Wilson, Thomas Woodrow, Pres. U.S., 1856-1924., 9 items (Folder 18)
- Window Rock, Arizona -- Views., 5 items (Box 85, Folder 19)
- Windsor Castle -- Views., 12 items (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Wing Ling., 2 items (Folder 21)
- Winn, A.M., 2 items (Folder 22)
- Winston, Maggie., 2 items (Folder 23)
- Witch Creek, San Diego Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 24)
- Witherby, Oliver S., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 25)
- Wodehouse, Pelham Grenville, 1881-1975, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Wolfskill (William) Ranch house, Los Angeles Co., Calif., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Wolfskill, William., 2 items (Box 85, Folder 27)
- Wood, Garfield Arthur, 1880-1971., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 29)
- Woods, Mark, 1901-, 1 item (Box 85, Folder 30)
- Woods, Robert., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Workman, Mrs. Fanny (Bullock), 1859-1928, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 32)
- Workman, William Henry, 1839-1918, -- Portrait., 5 items (Box 85, Folder 34)
- Workman, William, 1800-1876., 2 items (Box 85, Folder 33)
- Works, Alice (Banta)., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 35)
- World War 1939-1945 - California - Los Angeles. (Folder 1)
- World War, 1914-1918, -- Views., 28 items (Folder 36)
- World War, 1939-1945, -- Los Angeles, California -- Views., 11 items (Box 85, Folder 37)
- Wotton, Sir Henry, 1568-1639, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 38)
- Wright, Francis Marion, 1844-1917, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 39)
- Wright, Harold Bell, 1872-1944, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 40)
- Wright, Orville, 1871-1948, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 41)
- Wrightwood Lake, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 43)
- Wrightwood, Calif. -- Views., 25 items (Folder 42)
- Wyatt, Harry C. -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 44)
- Wyntoon, Shasta Co., Calif. -- Views., 4 items (Folder 45)
- Wyoming -- Views., 19 items (Box 85, Folder 46)
- Yates, Edmund Hodgson, 1831-1894, -- Portrait., 4 items (Box 85, Folder 47)
- Ybarra Family -- Portrait., 6 items (Folder 48)
- Yellowstone National Park -- Views., 71 items (Folder 49)
- Yorba Family., 9 items (Box 85, Folder 50)
- Yorke, Edward., 1 item (Box 85, Folder 51)
- Yosemite Naitonal Park -- Views., 58 items (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Bridal Veil Falls)., 9 items (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Camp Sites)., 6 items (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Cathedral Spires)., 3 items (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (El Capitan)., 6 items (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Falls)., 9 items (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Glacier Point)., 5 items (Folder 7)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Half Dome)., 18 items (Folder 8)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Hotels)., 5 items (Folder 9)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Merced River)., 18 items (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Mirror Lake)., 5 items (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Nevada Falls)., 12 items (Folder 12)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Sentinel Rock)., 4 items (Folder 13)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Sequoia Goves)., 8 items (Folder 14)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (The Three Brothers)., 1 item (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Transportation)., 14 items (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Vernal Falls)., 12 items (Folder 17)
- Yosemite National Park -- Views (Yosemite Falls)., 21 items (Folder 18)
- Young, Gordan Ray, 1886-1948, -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 19)
- Younger, Evelle Jansen, 1918-1989, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 86, Folder 20)
- Yount, George C., 2 items (Box 86, Folder 21)
- Yountville, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Yreka, Calif. -- Views., 28 items (Folder 23)
- Ysaye, Eugene, 1858-1931, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Yuma Stage., 1 item (Box 86, Folder 26)
- Yuma, Arizona., 1 item (Box 86, Folder 25)
- Zamorano Club, Los Angeles, 1946 -- Portrait., 11 items (Folder 28)
- Zamorano, Augustin Juan Vincente, 1798-1842, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Zangwill, Israel, 1864-1926., 7 items (Box 86, Folder 29)
- Zeitlin, Jacob, 1902-1987, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 86, Folder 30)
- Zerrahn, Carl, 1826-1909., 1 item (Box 86, Folder 31)
- Zoot Suit Riots, Los Angeles, Calif., -- Views., 3 items (Folder 32)